MANYU LAKHOTIA

+1(337)322-4192 \$\text{LakeMonYew@gmail.com} \$\text{https://portfolio.majorziploc.com}\$ https://www.linkedin.com/in/majorziploc/ \$\text{https://github.com/MajorZiploc}\$

Software Developer with 6+ years of work experience in developing web applications, documenting, stand alone applications, cicd, and databases; along with personal experience in art/design, scripting, web scraping, data analytics, and data cleaning.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frontend react, redux, jquery, css, sass, html, material ui, bootstrap, krita, inkscape, winforms, cypress.io

Backend/Testing/Headless django, express, nodejs, asp.net mvc, google app suite, jest, pandas, webscraper.io, tampermonkey

Languages javascript, python, typescript, bash, sql, mongodb, php, redis, java, C#, F#, powershell, rbql, vimscript

DevOps docker, aws, kubernetes, gitlab ci, github actions, ansible, Octopus Deploy, Teamcity, vmware

EXPERIENCE

Acadian Ambulance

Software Engineer - Full time - Remote - Team size: 4-8 Optimal Dynamics (Logistics)

Feb 2024 - Present New York, NY

• Utilized tools like: react, redux, postgresql, django, celery, rabbitmq, docker, redis, spring boot, bash, microservices, aws

Software Engineer - Full time - Remote - Team size: 4-8 Conservis (Agriculture)

May 2022 - Jan 2024 Minneapolis, MN

- Improved authentication by moving from homebrewed auth solution to keycloak
- Use krita and inkscape to design frontend mockups and create svg icons
- Utilized tools like: react, redux, postgresql, django, celery, rabbitmq, docker, redis, spring boot, bash, microservices, aws

Software Developer - Full time - Mostly Remote - Team size: 4-10

(Medical)

Mar 2020 - Apr 2022

 $La fayette, \ LA$

• Led development of an ambulance scheduling system

- Introduced automated UI and API testing using Cypress.io
- Utilized tools like: F#, C#, react, redux, wsl, mssql, docker, just, bash, microservices, aws, Octopus Deploy, Teamcity

Software Developer - Part time - Remote - Team size: 3-5 Cythereal (Cyber security)

Jun 2021 - Apr 2022

La fayette, LA

- Created dashboard to investigate potential malware samples
- Utilized tools like: django, react, redux, docker, mongodb, redis, rpm, bash, azure, ansible, terraform, packer, just

Software Developer - Full time - Hybrid - Team size: 10-15 CGI (Medical)

Jan 2019 - Feb 2020

Lafayette, LA

- Migrated legacy health insurance portal to more modern solutions
- Utilized tools like: django, react, redux, docker, redis, mongodb, bash, openshift, vscode

Research Assistant - Part time - Hybrid

May 2018 - Dec 2018

University Of Louisiana

(Programming Languages)

La fayette, LA

Software Developer - Full time - Hybrid - Team size: 4-6

 $\rm Dec~2016$ - $\rm Dec~2018$

Wetlands Research Center (Aquaculture)

La fayette, LA

• Developed a stand alone java swing app for analyzing geospatial water levels from large NetCDF files

OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS

 $\mathbf{F} \# \ \mathbf{projects} \ \mathbf{with} \ \mathbf{contributions} \ \mathbf{FSharpPlus}, \ \mathbf{Acadian.FSharp}, \ \mathbf{Acadian.Dapper.Fs}, \ \mathbf{Acadian.Json.Fs} \ (\mathbf{Available} \ \mathbf{on} \ \mathbf{nuget})$

keycloak A oauth2 library with user federations, management and more (Available on maven) (java)

nvim-dev-container A nvim plugin for remote devcontainers using same configs as vscode devcontainers (lua)

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Economics with Computer Science and Mathematics, University of Louisiana at Lafayette 2016 - 2018

Associates in General Studies Business, South Louisiana Community College

2013 - 2015